We just stretched out the hips so let's balance now our center or our core.
So Julie is going to lift up out of pigeon pose, swing that right leg around as you shift the weight into the left hip.
Then I'm going to place a blanket underneath the tail bone for this next position.
You may or may not need the blanket.
So you are going to bring the knees towards the chest, lift the heart towards the sky and then lean back a little bit, lifting the feet off the floor a tiny degree.
So that's one variation.
If you would like you can straighten the legs completely.
This is boat pose or navasana.
It is very trying on that center so breath deeply trying to keep the chest up, pretend that there is a nice candle and a flame flickering behind you and you want to lift away from that flame.
So you are keeping your boat out of the water, keeping the legs extended.
At any time if you feel pressure on the low back bend the knees or clasp the hands around the back side of the knees to release that pressure keeping the energy focused on the abdominals.
That's great.